A Guide to the Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder, 1993.
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
Constituent Correspondence of Governor Lawrence Douglas Wilder,
1993.
The Library of Virginia
34588
Virginia. Governor (1990-1994: Wilder).
24 cu. ft. (24 boxes)
Administrative Information
Arranged by series.
Access Restrictions
These records are open for research but it may be necessary for an archivist to review certain files before they can be used by patrons for research purposes or before any copies of the records can be made. Privacy protected and other protected information is considered confidential and restricted from public access for 75 years. If you are planning to use these records, please contact Archives Reference Services for additional details before planning your research trip.
Acquisition Information
Accession 34588 was transferred by Gov. Lawrence Douglas Wilder, January 14, 1994.
Historical Information
Lawrence Douglas Wilder was born in Richmond, Va., on January 17, 1931. He graduated from Virginia Union University in 1951 and afterwards was drafted into the Army, where he served in the Korean War from 1952-1953 and received a bronze star. He then attended the Howard University School of Law and graduated in 1959. Douglas Wilder was elected to the Virginia Senate in 1969 as the first African American member since Reconstruction and served in the Senate for five terms. In 1985, he was elected to the office of Lieutenant Governor as the first African American to be elected to statewide office in Virginia. L. Douglas Wilder won the election for Governor of Virginia in 1989 and served from January 13, 1990 to January 14, 1994. He was the first African American to be elected as Governor in United States.
The Office of Constituent Affairs was first established in 1984 to serve as a liaison between the Governor and the citizens of the Commonwealth. The Office oversees and coordinates responses to all mail sent to the Governor's Office. Constituent Affairs staff determine where and under whose signature the responses should be drafted and direct correspondence to the appropriate person in the administration. The Office also answers phone inquiries from constituents and occasionally meets with constituents to resolve problems and handle requests. William R. Browning served as Director of Constituent Affairs during the Wilder Administration.
Scope and Content
Constituent Correspondence, 1993, is housed in 24 boxes and consists of letters received by Governor Wilder from citizens, public officials, and various organizations. Correspondence in this series usually includes an accompanying Response Referral Form, and an attached copy of the response from the Governor or the appropriate Secretary, state agency, or Governor's Office staff member. The Response Referral Form includes date received, topic, to whom the letter is referred, and instructions. Constituent correspondence includes invitations, requests for assistance, and statements of concern or inquiries on a variety of issues. Constituent correspondence also includes limited correspondence from federal and state agencies, local government officials, Virginia General Assembly members, members of the U.S. Congress, and others, including the U.S. President, governors of other states, and ambassadors.
Constituent Correspondence, 1993, is divided into three series: Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies; Series II. Governor's Office; and Series III. Scheduling Office. Correspondence is arranged by topic and includes mail on a variety of subjects, including administration initiatives and specific legislative actions. Also includes mail from habitual writers, and mass mailings, which often consist of form letters and signed petitions.
Arrangement
This collection is arranged into the following series:
Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1993
Series II. Governor's Office, 1993
Series III. Scheduling Office, 1993.
Contents List
- Series I. Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies, 1993., Extent: 13 cubic feet (13 boxes). (Box 1-13)
  Cabinet Secretaries and State Agencies correspondence, is housed in 13 boxes and is arranged alphabetically by Cabinet Secretary, and alphabetically by topic or state agency within each Secretarial area. This series includes correspondence received by the Governor's Office that was directed to Cabinet Secretaries or state agencies for response. Includes original letter, Response Referral Form, and attached response.
  - Secretary of Administration: Compensation Board, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Administration: Early retirement, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Administration: Employee Relations Counselors, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Administration: Equal Employment, Office of, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Administration: General (1 of 5), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Administration: General (2 of 5), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Administration: General (3 of 5), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Administration: General (4 of 5), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Administration: General (5 of 5), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Services, Dept of (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Services, Dept. of (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Administration: General Sevices, Dept. of (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Administration: Grievances, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Administration: Health insurance benefits, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Administration: Health insurance benefits - Key Advantage Plan, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Administration: Human Rights, Council on, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Administration: Information Management, Council of, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Administration: Information Technology, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Administration: Local Government, Commission on, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Administration: Personnel and Training, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Administration: Purchase and Supply, Division of, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Administration: Salaries, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Administration: State Board of Elections, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Administration: Veterans Affairs, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Retirement System, 1993. (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Administration: Virginia Supplemental Retiremen System (Pensions), 1993. (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Agriculture, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Block Grant, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Commerce, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Consumer Affairs, Division of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Contractors, Board of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Cosmetology, Board of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Defense, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Disaster areas (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Disaster areas (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Downsizing Action, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Earned Income Tax Credit, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Energy, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Forestry, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Fortune 500 Forum, 1993. (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (1 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (2 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (3 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (4 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (5 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (6 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (7 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (8 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (9 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (10 of 12), 1993. (Box 2, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (11 of 12), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: General (12 of 12), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Homeless Intervention Program, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Community Development, Dept. of - Homelessness, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing and Urban Developmnet, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Housing Partnership Program, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Information Technology, Center of, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Japan External Trade Organization, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Labor and Industry, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Milk Commission, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Mines, Minerals and Energy, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Minority Business Enterprise, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Pickett Road Tank Farm, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Real Estate, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Redskin Stadium, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Relocation to/in Virginia, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Rural Development, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Small Business Administration, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Tourism, Division of, 1993. (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Employment Commission (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Festival of American Films, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Housing Development Agency, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Mainstreet Program, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Port Authority, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: Virginia Racing Commission, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Economic Development: World Trade, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: Arts, Commission for the, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: College of William and Mary, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: College, Christopher Newport, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: College, Longwood, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: College, Mary Washington, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: College, Northern Virginia Community, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: Cooperative Extension Services, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: Drug Prevention, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: Frontier Culture Museum of Virginia, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: General (1 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: General (2 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: General (3 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Education: General (4 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Education: General (5 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Education: General (6 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Education: General (7 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Education: General (8 of 8), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Education: Governor's School Program, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Education: Higher Education, State Council on (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Education: Higher Education, State Council on (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Education: Innovation Technology, Center for, 1993. (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Education: Institute, Virginia Military (VMI), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Education: Institute, Virginia Polytechnic and State University (VPISU, Virginia Tech), 1993. (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - Secretary of Education: Jamestown-Yorktown Foundation, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Education: National Air and Space Museum, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Education: School Board, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Education: School funding, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Education: School Violence Prevention, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Education: Science Museum of Virginia, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Education: State Education Assistance Authority, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Education: Teacher salaries, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Education: Tuition Assistance Grant Program, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Education: University of Virginia, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Education: University, George Mason, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Education: University, James Madison, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Education: University, Norfolk State, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Education: University, Old Dominion, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Education: University, Radford, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Education: Universiy, Virginia Commonwealth, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Education: University, Virginia State, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Education: University, Virginia Union, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Community College System, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Education Loan Authority, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia Museum of Fine Arts, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Education: Virginia State Library and Archives, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Finance: Accounts, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Finance: Energy Tax, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Finance: Federal Tobacco Tax, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Finance: Planning and Budget, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Finance: Sales Tax, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 27)
  - Secretary of Finance: State Budget Revenue, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 28)
  - Secretary of Finance: State Internal Auditor, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 29)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Cigarette tax (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 30)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Cigarette tax (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 6, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Cigarette tax (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 6, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Cigarette tax (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 6, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 31)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 32)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 33)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 6, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Comptroller, Office of the (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 34)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Comptroller, Office of the (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 35)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Comptroller, Office of the (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 5, Folder 36)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Federal Pensions/Retirees, 1993. (Box 5, Folder 37)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Income tax assessment (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 6, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Income tax assessment, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Lottery proceeds, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Property Tax, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Real Estate Tax, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Social Security, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Finance: Taxation, Dept. of - Escheats, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Finance: Treasury, Dept. of the, 1993. (Box 6, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Abortion, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Adolescent pregnancy, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Adoption, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Aging, Dept. for, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Birth-Related Neurological Injury Compensation Program, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Central State Hosptial, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Certificate of Public Need, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child abuse, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child custody, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child Day Care and Early Childhood, Council on, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child support (1 of 4), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child support (2 of 4), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child support (3 of 4), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Child support (4 of 4), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Community Services Block Grant, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Deaf and Hard of Hearing, Dept. for the, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Eastern State Hosptial, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Food Bank, 1993. (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (1 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (2 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (3 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (4 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (5 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (6 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (7 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (8 of 9), 1993. (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: General (9 of 9), 1993. (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Governor's Employment and Training Dept., 1993. (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Care, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Professions, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Service Cost Review Council, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Health Service Cost Review Council, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: HIV/AIDS, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Human Rights, Council on, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Indians, Council on, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Indoor Clean Air Act (1 of 2), 1993. (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Indoor Clean Air Act (2 of 2), 1993. (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Infant mortality, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Job Training Partnership Act, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medicaid, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medical Assistance Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Medicine, Board of, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of (1 of 3), 1993. (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of (2 of 3), 1993. (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Mental Health, Mental Retardation and Substance Abuse, Dept. of (3 of 3), 1993. (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Nursing, Board of, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Rehabilitative Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Rights of the Disabled, 1993. (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Security, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 1)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (1 of 5), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 2)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (2 of 5), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 3)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (3 of 5), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 4)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (4 of 5), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 5)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Social Services, Dept. of (5 of 5), 1993. (Box 9, Folder 6)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Status of Women, Council on the, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 7)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Visually Impaired, Dept. for the, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 8)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Vital Records, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 9)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Volunteerism, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 10)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Western State Hospital, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 11)
  - Secretary of Health and Human Resources: Youth and Family Services, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 12)
  - Secretary of Natural Resources: Air Pollution Control, Dept. of, 1993. (Box 9, Folder 13)